lilwaynehq.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy for LilWayneHQ.com

_Effective May 27, 2018. Last Revised May 27, 2018_

This privacy policy sets out how [LilWayneHQ.com](https://www.lilwaynehq.com/ "LilWayneHQ.com") and our [Forum](https://www.lilwaynehq.com/forums "LilWayneHQ Forum") uses and protects any information that you provide, whilst using our services.

LilWayneHQ is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Any information provided by you to us, by which you can be identified, will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

It is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy from time to time as we may make changes to it and so you will need to make sure that you agree with any of the changes made.

**What information do we collect?**  
When signing up to the LilWayneHQ.com Forum, we will require a username, a valid e-mail address, a password, and a birth date. We will also store your account settings and preferences.

Registration requires a valid e-mail address and members will not be able to create new threads or post to discussions without one. Members will also have their accounts deleted if they do not confirm their e-mail address after 1 month. You have the ability to keep your e-mail address hidden from other members by selecting that option in your [Settings](https://www.lilwaynehq.com/forums/usercp.php "LilWayneHQ Forum Settings").

Your username will be public, but it does not have to be related to your real name.

A birth date is to make sure you are not under the age of 13, or else you will be required to get parental consent before posting on the LilWayneHQ Forum. You have the option of hiding your birthday from other members in your [Settings](https://www.lilwaynehq.com/forums/usercp.php "LilWayneHQ Forum Settings").

You can decide how much other personal information is visible in your [Settings](https://www.lilwaynehq.com/forums/usercp.php "LilWayneHQ Forum Settings"), such as location, occupation, gender, biography, interests, and homepage URL. If you have any concerns about providing this information, please leave these fields blank.

We also collect the content you submit to the LilWayneHQ Forum. This includes your threads, posts, and private messages.

Additionally, whilst using the LilWayneHQ Forum, your IP address will be collected. If you purchase a service from us that lets you access other areas of the website, we will collect payment information from you, such as your PayPal address.

When using the [Contact form](https://www.lilwaynehq.com/contact/ "Contact LilWayneHQ.com") on this site, your message and e-mail address will be forwarded to the owner’s personal e-mail, which means none of your personal information will be stored on the web server.

For our commenting system, we use Disqus’ comments system, which involves the use of Disqus Inc. cookies.

**What do we do with the information we collect?**  
The information you provide to the LilWayneHQ.com Forum is required for, but not limited to, the following reasons:

• Internal record keeping.  
• Access to the LilWayneHQ.com Forum.  
• User management.  
• User confirmation and user reset.

**How do we secure the information?**  
We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to the LilWayneHQ.com Forum is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or private information hacked, we have put in place suitable electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. We also use HTTPS while information is being transmitted.

**How do we use cookies and IP addresses?**  
The LilWayneHQ.com Forum involves the use of “cookies”, which are small text files that store information in your web browser. This includes remembering your session log in, which also helps track to read the last posts when you re-visit the website, HTTP information, preferences, and IP address.

You have the option to turn these cookies off at any time by updating your web browser preferences. We advise that you to do so if you use a shared, public, or hospital computer. You can also log out after each session to prevent unauthorized access under your account. If your browser does not support cookies, or if you have cookies turned off, these preferences will not be set.

Users who sign up, create posts, send private messages, or perform any other action that results in data being transferred to or from your computer/device and to the LilWayneHQ Forum will have their IP address stored in our database.

Your IP address is not visible to the public at any time.

**Links to other websites:**  
LilWayneHQ.com and our Forum may contain links to other websites. These sites may or may not be affiliated with us. We have no control over any external sites, so if you click on a link which results into you visiting an external site, this Privacy Policy will no longer be applied and LilWayneHQ cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide whilst visiting such websites.

**Controlling your personal information:**  
LilWayneHQ.com and our Forum value your privacy. Your registration information and any other details you place on our website are subject to our Privacy Policy. Any and all personal information you provide to us will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, disclosed, shared, or loaned to anyone outside of LilWayneHQ unless we have your explicit permission, or are required by law to do so.

We may use your personal information to send you security information, or other information related to LilWayneHQ and your account.

If you discover any of the information that LilWayneHQ holds for you is incorrect or incomplete, which you are unable to change yourself, please [contact us](https://www.lilwaynehq.com/contact/ "Contact LilWayneHQ.com") as soon as possible, so the correct changes can be made.

**Ads and Analytics Partners:**  
LilWayneHQ.com and our Forum may partner with third-party advertisers, ad networks, and analytics providers to deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests. These third parties may collect information sent by your computer, web browser, or mobile device in response to a request for content, such as unique identifiers, your IP address, or other information about your computer or device.

Our ad partners and ad networks may use cookies and related technologies to collect information when ads are delivered to you on our website, but LilWayneHQ does not link to, or provide them with your actual account details. This means that we do not share your individual account browsing habits with advertisers. We cannot see advertisers’ cookies and advertisers will not see our cookies.

We use analytics partners, such as Google Analytics, to help analyze usage, traffic, and the number of unique visitors on LilWayneHQ.

**Rights:**  
You have a right to access the personal data we hold about you, or obtain a copy of it. To do so, please [contact us](https://www.lilwaynehq.com/contact/ "Contact LilWayneHQ.com"). If you believe that the information we hold for you is incomplete or inaccurate, you may [contact us](https://www.lilwaynehq.com/contact/ "Contact LilWayneHQ.com") and ask us to complete or correct that information.

You also have the right to request the erasure of your personal data. Please [contact us](https://www.lilwaynehq.com/contact/ "Contact LilWayneHQ.com") if you would like us to remove your personal data.

**Acceptance of this policy:**  
Continued use of LilWayneHQ.com marks your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept our policy then please do not use this website. When registering we will further request your explicit acceptance of this policy.

**Changes to this policy:**  
LilWayneHQ.com may make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future. We will also let you know if it has changed by revising the date at the top of this policy.
